Tokimeki Manzeta, Junction TV!
Yay!
Nice to meet you.
Oh, nice to meet you.
All of us are a group.
Yes, so this time, let me ask you this,
How are you guys doing lately?
I feel good.
How are you doing lately?
Still teaching life.
I'm teaching life.
It's great.
Yes, it is.
Yes.
Good song.
Marriage, you say, grows?
It grows.
Junction TV.
So, you grew up, and what do you do today?
What do you do when you grow up?
Where do we show them?
Where to show.
Where will we show them?
Today, let's all connect the circle of karma,
The Rengo Game!
Yay!
Are you good at drawing?
Yes, I am.
Oh!
I'm getting confidence once again.
I'm getting it now.
Yes, I am.
This time, the staff gave me a theme for the picture,
For example, Kanami was asked to draw a dog.
Kanami draws a picture of a dog.
Then, she shows it to Julia.
Then she shows it to Julia. I'm going.
I'm going.
Twice. I don't know what that means, but it's a cat.
Oh, it's a cat. A cat.
Okay, I'll go.
Oh, it's a bear.
So, Hiyori wrote a bear in the end,
This turn is a failure.
Failure.
That was easy to understand now, wasn't it?
I was trying to connect pictures together like this,
If you stop putting this in, it will be a correct answer.
It's the first one, right?
It's the limit of the limit.
Why?
If we don't succeed,
From the manager,
I'm sorry you're all going to miss dinner tonight.
To the parents.
Parents.
Why, everyone in the household,
There's no dinner.
Oh no.
There's a game for the bears.
It's a game for bears, isn't it?
Oh no.
Let's do our best.
You think it's remote control?
Let's succeed so our parents won't worry.
Let's all maintain our hearts and minds.
Okay, I'd like to start with the first turn.
First, goo, doo, three, nice!
Yes, sir.
We have to go that far.
Hiyori's.
Something happened.
I wonder what happened.
Okay, so I'll be first.
Oh, no!
Good luck, An-chan!
Please give me a subject.
I'll do my best.
Oh, no...
What?
I can't do it.
You can't.
Come on, man.
I can't do it. - What? You can't do it?
Thirty seconds?
What are you doing?
Isn't 30 seconds too short?
Short!
30 seconds for low power.
Oh, God, I can't do it anymore.
I can't do it.
I can't do it!
This is too hard!
Nothing's impossible.
It's okay.
Are we going to make it? Remember.
What time do you want to eat?
What do you think they're having for dinner?
I'm already hungry.
I had a craving earlier.
Wait, what else? What was that?
Are you okay, Kamo?
Are we done?
I can't do this!
This is a terrible idea!
It's not fair!
I know the words and I know the whole thing.
Okay?
I'm in!
That's what I was gonna do.
I'm going.
Oh, my God!
What?
If you let your imagination run wild, you'll see.
Oh, my God!
Ew!
What is it?
You didn't do it once?
What?
Explain it, then explain it.
Okay, Julia, let's go.
Are we done?
Wait, wait, wait.
I can't do it. It's been 30 seconds.
But you know what? I think it's a pretty good fight, don't you?
Yeah, I think so.
Hey.
Good luck, Caramie. - What?
What, 30 seconds?
You're lying.
Are you okay?
What is it?
I can do it. I can do it.
Wait a minute.
Are we done?
You can do it.
Then you can do it.
I can't do that.
I can't do it.
Okay, okay.
Then you don't look good.
I'll win looking like that.
Hey.
Oh, my God.
You look too good.
What?
It's okay.
Oh, here.
What the hell is that?
What's this?
Maybe it's a toy giveaway.
I don't know where to start.
Oh, there's still time
You're looking at it
I don't know.
Why?
Added originality.
Oh, God.
OK.
Okay.
It's okay.
Ha-ha-ha.
Help me.
Come back, come back, come back, come back.
What's going on?
Help me.
Are you in here?
Are you there? Do you know?
You don't know?
What is this?
No, I think I know what you mean.
It's a terrible subject.
What's this?
Oh, I mean, the Japanese theme is terrible.
What's this? What's this?
Oh, here we go.
Yeah, okay.
Oh, man, it's not that much.
There's a little hope for you, Healy.
Healy?
No, no, this is something.
I know exactly what this is.
What's this?
Oh, well, uh..,
Oh, uh..,
Uh, it's live.
Oh, no.
It's not that you can't beat me.
Last one today.
What?
Oh,
No, I'm still number one.
Wow, that's nice.
Hey, that's terrible!
It's a terrible theme.
You like it?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You ready?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, my God!
What?
What's going on?
Oh, my God.
Ten seconds.
10 seconds!
Oh, my God.
Isn't that one time first place?
I think we're in first place once.
Oh, I'm sorry. I think I got it wrong.
Oh, wait a minute.
One down.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Here.
This one.
1st place
Number one.
what's that?
I did it!
That's great.
Okay, then.
Next.
I'll get the answer.
Where to?
Toner the locomotive.
Toner.
Certainly.
I'm sure.
It's cool.
It sure looks like one, doesn't it?
Definitely.
I'm sure.
He presented this kind of life.
Okay, Hiyori.
I'll take care of it.
What?
What's with Doraemon?
I wonder if he wants to write a book.
Ah...
No.
This one too.
Mom, please
Doraemon...
In a weird way...
What's that?
Stairs?
Yes, up.
It's funny.
It's like heaven.
Oh, my God.
But only for me.
This is
Absolutely hilarious.
I'm...
Doraemon and
and the little cucumber...
Where is... where is... where is...
The firecracker...
A firefly...
What?
That's...
That's a first.
It's the first time.
Why are they combined here?
It's all over the place.
They're merging.
I made a mistake.
Um...
What?
You're eye-balling me.
Your ears.
What do you mean?
Oh, shit.
Oh, my God.
Seriously, it's gonna cost you an eye.
Let me see your mom's.
Here we go.
I wrote this.
I'm serious.
What?
Oh, the new engine.
Mario.
Oh, Mario.
New Engine.
New Engine
Mario's
USJ.
It's USJ
It's USJ.
It's not going to end, is it?
This, this, this.
It's not going to end.
This is...
It's a new engine.
It's like a strobe.
To get it out.
I wrote this for the time being
And
This is Mario
Mario thought it was...
He wanted to grow.
I'm impressed.
Mario's
Mother
Write alone
White Mario
No one can read
They don't want to see the bell.
Really?
I don't want to see the bell.
Next time, go to the bell.
To see the bell.
Don't miss it!
See you later.
It's hard to find the time
Time is difficult
I can write in 30 seconds.
This is what USJ is all about.
I can write it in 30 seconds
I'm tearing up
But with this.
Julia's new engine.
Isn't that great?
That's great.
Surprisingly.
So many things here.
There's no food, is there?
There's no rice, is there?
There's no rice
There is no rice
There's no rice.
First, goo, then rock, paper, scissors, then rock, paper, scissors.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
Next, "goo", rock-paper-scissors, then "jankenpou", then "julia", then "julia", then "julia".
Julia's here! She's here! Hoshiki!
That's right, staff, they're coming from far away.
Hoshiki and Hoshiki. The first one is different.
The first one!
Really, give me a break!
Please.
What?
I didn't hear your nickname.
I didn't hear it.
Maybe he can.
I'm listening.
What?
I didn't hear you.
Oh, my God.
That was different.
Hey, that's good.
That's good, Haru-chan.
That's Cardi's Maria from earlier.
That's the one, right, Grandpa?
You got the important stuff wrong.
Can you say it? Say it! Here we go! Ready!
I don't understand this.
Are you writing it already?
I did.
Then you know it.
My drawing.
Please.
Is it easier than the first time?
It's all right.
I got it!
You can do it!
Good luck!
Thank you!
Sorry.
The camera's out!
Can you do it?
Okay, okay.
Oh!
Okay, okay, okay.
I wrote the request.
Hurry up, hurry up, hurry up, hurry up.
Hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry
From the mouth of a crow, hurry hurry hurry hurry
Not much is coming out
Okay, okay, okay
Wait a minute
Hiyori, you can do it!
I can do it! I can do it!
You have five seconds.
But... but...
What? Nice to meet you.
Calm down. Give me the letters.
It's so different.
But, no, it's not partial.
It's a big, big change.
It's important to have the right amount of comfort.
I knew I ordered a billion zillion zillion zillion zillion zillion.
You're eating the whole thing.
It's a very small mind-numbing to put out the word.
Which is very small. 1969.
The man who played the conducive role.
The old man's girl
it's so hard to be in love
Song, from earlier
Oh, here it comes, here it comes
Oh, here it comes.
She's here? Really?
Easier? Easier than before.
Much easier.
I love it.
What the hell?
First, you do this.
Like this.
Regard.
Here we go.
I'm nervous.
I'm nervous at the end.
And then...
This part.
We'll sing it together.
Oh! I think I got it!
But what's the name of it?
Name?
No, I... it's... it's... it's... it's for you to see.
What's it say?
I don't know if I can do this anymore.
What?
I think I might be screwed.
What? What? What?
What? What's wrong?
What's up?
What? But...
But...
What? What?
What is it?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Sorry.
What?
Okay.
What's this?
Wait a minute. What is this? I have no idea.
Is this one of them?
A cluster?
But no.
What? What's this?
It's easy to see.
A TV?
Oh, I got this one, too.
Do you need this?
What?
What do you have?
Here, baby.
What?
Oh, my God!
Oh, my gosh.
A party.
There's a party.
What's this?
Hitoko, please answer.
I don't understand. I copied it.
What's this?
That kind of thing.
Please.
What is this?
Is it coming?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Is this it? What is this?
I don't know.
A person?
Lights?
Yummy.
What, what, what, what?
Aki, please.
Movie theater?
Movie theater.
Movie theater!
So it's my fault.
No, it's my fault.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
These two.
Is that moon?
Is that a club?
And here.
This is moon here.
She's working with the dolls.
It's all fluttery.
Rugby.
But at first.
I thought it was a school.
I thought it was a bear, like a teacher's bear.
A teacher...
I don't know... normal.
But...
But here's what I figured out.
I see.
You're good here.
We're pretty split up.
I figured it out.
I got it.
I can do it. I can do it.
One more time.
Okay, more and more.
Ten, ten, ten, ten, ten.
Oh, you still got it?
Not yet!
Did we lose?
I should have told him.
Oh, no, we lost number one.
I don't know.
Did we lose?
Wow!
Scary.
That's nice.
Ah, aggressive!
Wait for the color
Unhappy
Products
Satandi
Beauty Rabbit
What do you think?
I don't know. I think it's not good.
What?
Does it change once you take the paint off the handle?
Does it say what color it is?
Uh, sorry.
I'm not paying.
Here, matches.
Okay, I think we're done here.
Come on!
What? Huh?
Huh? Huh?
Ho!
Huh!
Hate!
Come on!
They're all like this, aren't they?
How do I express myself?
Don't be sorry anymore
It's not over yet
It's not over.
Hazukasan!
Earthly energy
Let's do events together from now on!
This is today's club activity.
One by one for me
I'm so excited to be a part of it! I'm so excited to be a part of it!
Something different, right?
Victory
It jumped out at me.
I'm writing in 10 seconds.
The pictures are flowing.
A freebie?
Bisho?
They're all losers.
You're not missing anything.
Is it that hard?
What?
Ten seconds.
I'm writing.
That could be it.
Yeah, it could be this.
No, it's not.
Oh, look at this.
Look at this.
Oh, my God.
Is that me?
You look good.
Voice
Ahhh...
Oh, that.
Or is it different?
No?
No, no, no, no, no, that could be it.
It could be.
That's the right thing to do.
It is, isn't it?
Am I wrong?
Okay, I'll answer that.
Here we go.
Set.
Oh, no.
How's that?
Here we go.
What's this?
Did you copy it?
Dokishen.
Six.
No, you didn't.
Super-dokin'.
Doxichen
Re-teach Tsumoro
I say kagura pin.
I see.
Wait a minute.
It's going to change to about three people.
I'm going to put about three people over it.
Like Ferris.
I'll put three people on top of each other.
From the middle.
Me, O'Haro, and about three other people
Put three people on top of each other.
Hey.
I'm not going to cover all three of us.
I'm trying to remember Akichan's and my hair.
I'm thinking of Julia's haircut.
I'm going to put all three of you in it.
It's hard.
It's so hard to do, isn't it?
This is what's so great about the comment section.
So cute.
This can't be the first two.
Okay, okay.
Let's go next.
Come on, come on, come on.
Oh, last one again?
I did the first one.
All the way at the end.
Okay, please.
I feel like I'm gonna die.
You're asking me to leave now?
Please don't tell me you've heard this before.
What's with the fireman Zoli?
What's with the firefighting Zorri?
It's fun.
What is it?
Please!
Hold back!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
That's disgusting.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Are you sick?
What?
But you know what?
Why are you making a mistake?
You have to put it in properly.
Get it right!
What's this?
He says it's disgusting.
I don't know how to feel.
Oh, my God, this feeling.
This again?
What is this?
But this...
Oh, please.
What?
Oh, God.
All right, here we go.
Ready?
There you go.
Is it still the same?
Just as I thought.
Oh?
What?
I don't want to make excuses.
Trust me, I'm thrilled to be here.
Anytime, anytime, anytime hot.
I love this new world so much.
I wish I could do that for you.
I wish I could
Anytime, anytime
I love it so much
A new world.
What is this? You don't understand?
I can do it, I can do it, I can do it.
I can do it. I can do it. Okay, Kaboom, here we go.
Here you go.
Is that it?
No, it's not.
Just look at the picture.
Okay.
Let's turn it into a turnip.
What will it be?
I don't know.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Is this it?
But it's just what I thought.
This one?
Can I keep it as I thought?
That's it, right? It's right, right?
Yes, it's right.
Because that's him.
What?
Because he's the one.
Hey.
Is it a person? A person?
Tell him about Julia.
Tell me about Julia.
That's not an answer.
Yes, it is.
That's definitely the answer.
Oh, that's it.
Just the absolute last one.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha
That's the one.
He's the best I've ever seen.
He was a great guy.
Probably.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Yes.
Yes, you do.
Yes, yes.
Yes, please.
Vaccine
Yes, yes, yes.
uh
Good night.
Oh, shit.
By the way...
I'm fine.
That's disgusting.
Good.
Clear.
We did it.
That's it.
Yay!
Worst
Worst!
LOL!
It's all thanks to this.
Physical fitness.
My stamina was good.
Laughs.
Physical fitness.
Too much fun.
Laughter
Laughter on my face
LOL
I cleared it.
It was fun!
Yay!
Thank you very much.
I was looking forward to it.
For being an idiot.
It was good.
The power of the picture
The power of imagination
Let's work on your imagination
I'll do my best.
LOL.
Thanks for watching.
Bye-bye.
Subscribe to our channel
Goodbye goodbye, thank you for yesterday, after the rain, the streets are turning colors
Paint a piece of the future on the canvas of my broken heart and let it guide me.
Subtitle: Kiyohiroiyo
Now I can tell you the reason for my tears
Whenever you're lost, just remember
When it's raining, I'll smile
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye Goodbye to Yesterday's Me
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
My heart is fine as I've grown accustomed to it, rainbow pools, rainbow sounds
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
My accustomed heart is sunny, spilling tears out of my heart
I'll wear a rainbow dress
LaLaLaLa...
Please subscribe to our channel!